import { Question } from "../App";

export const tbbtData: Question[] =
    [
        {
            "question": "What is Sheldon's catchphrase?",
            "options": ["Bazinga!", "Eureka!", "Gotcha!", "Boom!"],
            "answer": "Bazinga!"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Sheldon's roommate?",
            "options": ["Leonard", "Raj", "Howard", "Stuart"],
            "answer": "Leonard"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of the comic book store owner?",
            "options": ["Stuart", "Barry", "Bert", "Wil"],
            "answer": "Stuart"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character is an astronaut?",
            "options": ["Howard", "Raj", "Leonard", "Sheldon"],
            "answer": "Howard"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Sheldon's girlfriend who later becomes his wife?",
            "options": ["Amy", "Penny", "Bernadette", "Leslie"],
            "answer": "Amy"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character has selective mutism and struggles to speak to women?",
            "options": ["Raj", "Howard", "Leonard", "Sheldon"],
            "answer": "Raj"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is Sheldon's favorite number?",
            "options": ["73", "42", "7", "21"],
            "answer": "73"
        },
        {
            "question": "What kind of engineer is Howard Wolowitz?",
            "options": ["Aerospace Engineer", "Electrical Engineer", "Mechanical Engineer", "Chemical Engineer"],
            "answer": "Aerospace Engineer"
        },
        {
            "question": "What is the name of Leonard's mother?",
            "options": ["Beverly", "Mary", "Debbie", "Emily"],
            "answer": "Beverly"
        },
        {
            "question": "What song does Sheldon like to be sung when heâ€™s sick?",
            "options": ["Soft Kitty", "Twinkle Twinkle Little Star", "Rock-a-bye Baby", "Mary Had a Little Lamb"],
            "answer": "Soft Kitty"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which character is known for their obsession with Star Wars?",
            "options": ["Sheldon", "Leonard", "Howard", "Raj"],
            "answer": "Sheldon"
        }
    ]
